I didn't think Lana'd find someone to cover a shift this late in the game.
Guess I should have figured on the Clark factor.
Well, it sounded like she was having her own crisis over Jensen's history exam.
Thanks for coming.
I know this can't compete with the all-you-can-drink talent cram session.
Definitely not.
Pete, I think it's great that you spent so much time volunteering here.
Well, someone's always been there for me when I've been in trouble.
It seems like a good way to give something back.
Hi, Pete.
And to hone your sensitive guy skills.
Watch and learn.
Team Crisis Hotline.
Uh-huh.
Well, how long's it been since they've been divorced?
Yeah, I know. That can be tough.
Well, have you talked to them about it?
Yeah.
Team Crisis Hotline.
Clark!
Lana.
Clark, it's happening!
Lana?
He's got a gun!
And a shotgun.
And gun!
61 to 65.
Clark!
Please, help me!
Lana?
Lana, when?
Lana.
Ah!
Lana?
Lana, can you hear me?
Lana!
Pete, call the police.
Hey, please hold.
Hold.
Hey, Clark.
Knock much?
You're too late.
Turned off the cappuccino machine an hour ago.
Somebody save me.
Let your warm hands break right through.
Don't care how you do it.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
I've been waiting.
I've been waiting for you.
I've made this whole world shine for you.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Help me.
Lana.
The call came from a blocked ID.
Sounds like your voice, Ms. Lang.
I know, but it can't be.
We think it's some sort of a prank, Chef.
Usually these situations originate a little closer to home than you'd expect.
Any reason you might want to goose these boys with a little crank call, Ms. Lang?
Lana didn't have anything to do with this.
Unless Miss Lang has grown several inches and developed an affinity for plaid,
this would be a good time for you to pipe down.
I suppose someone could be imitating you.
Why would anyone do that?
If I had the answer to half the whys in this town,
I'd have a bestseller on my hands.
I'll look into this.
But you kids need to know that crank calls aren't exactly a top priority, huh?
You okay?
You know, if someone's doing this as a joke,
they have a pretty sick sense of humor.
Don't worry. We'll figure out who did this.
This connection's bad. We're missing pieces of the conversation.
But the background noise is constant throughout.
This recording wasn't piecemealed together.
Here.
I'll play it again with the static as low as I can get it.
That sounds like rain.
We haven't had a storm in months.
What is happening?
Why would I say that?
It's almost like you were expecting something.
Eric! Eric, help me!
You heard me!
Hey, Chloe. Can I?
Yeah.
I think I heard something.
You heard me!
We were divey, minuscule.
So I usd.
Yeah.
Steph and notices.
Their
So you don't want to back up.
Yes.
This has got to be a recording of an old game.
No, they can't be.
This is the first year the Vipers have been defeated.
They're not even scheduled to play the Metros until tonight.
And according to the weather service, a storm's on the way.
Well, if none of this has happened yet,
maybe the phone call hasn't either.
You're saying the call came from the future?
What is this?
Experimental medication.
Not exactly FDA approved,
but I assume you're working on the patent.
Oh, Nix, I don't have time for 2020.
I'm sorry.
I have a few questions.
I know about the lab at Metron.
It gives new meaning to the term human resources.
You know, there are hundreds of projects in development at Luther Corp.
You'll have to forgive me if I'm not current
on all the details about, uh, what, Metron?
You're secretly developing a serum
that has a certain Lazarus effect on the dearly departed?
Resuscitating the dead?
I think your, uh, creative talents
are being wasted at Luther Corp. some.
Unfortunately, this isn't fiction.
So far, the, uh, Kafkaesque trials
have caused patients' bodies to deteriorate
while their minds retain consciousness.
Sort of bypasses the code of ethics,
but I suppose if you were successful,
it could mean big business.
I applaud your moral outrage, but, um,
you know, these papers don't, uh,
specifically confirm any of your accusations, son.
Although they would raise a few eyebrows to the Daily Planner.
You know, you don't have to resort to threats, Lex,
if you want to shut this project down.
I must not be making myself clear.
I came back to Luther Corp to be your partner,
not a paper pusher.
This new project can make the company billions of dollars.
I don't want it shut down.
I want to be put in charge of it.
What are you doing?
This is the restricted area.
Apparently not.
I'm not going to be able to do it.
I'm going to be a doctor.
You failed to mention, Dr. Tang,
that my son recently paid you a visit.
I don't know how he found us,
but I didn't tell him anything.
Well, it's irrelevant now, because as of this moment,
this project never existed.
But we haven't even tested the most recent adjustments.
Don't worry, Dr. Tang. Your work will continue.
Just not here.
I want this lab cleared out by the end of the day.
Or this time, you will find yourself deported
back to your native homeland.
And if I'm not mistaken,
your government does not have much use
for women who have, uh,
consorted with the devils of, uh,
Western capitalism.
Come on.
Am I right?
I knew this was all over the place,
and I'm not sure why it's not.
I don't know.
But, uh, we are.
We are not.
We are.
Shh.
Where have you been?
I'm sorry, Adam.
I know you're in a lot of pain.
I didn't want you to do this to me.
We were trying to give you a second chance.
I've been hearing a lot of noise out there.
What's going on?
They're shutting down the lab.
Where are we going?
You're not taking me with you.
I can't.
What about the medicine?
The medicine?
Mr. Luther took all of it.
Get it back!
I've only got 12 hours.
You know that!
He won't help you, Adam.
He doesn't even know you're alive.
I have no idea where he's taking the serum.
I'm sorry.
What am I supposed to do?
Look, even then, there's a lot going on.
You don't know Get outö
Listen guys, we just had a phenomenal reporter
in Los Angeles search for you for missing you.
Last night.
He ruined your Bucharest trip.
Yeah.
Tell me about your scheduled mission.
You.
All this because I was coming to New York,
and when I saw your
vonis looking damn what's called echo.
What's that to you?
He called this thing out, hard work.
Think about it.
Clark, what have you been doing?
Following me?
Don't turn this around on me, Lex.
Look, we think Adam died of liver disease a few months ago, and I'm guessing he was
one of Dr. Tang's subjects.
Lana's in trouble, and I know you're holding out on me.
Where is he, Lex?
You don't want anything to happen to Lana.
I know you don't.
Please.
Trust me, Clark.
There's no way Adam's gonna come after Lana.
How can you be so sure?
Because he can't leave the lab.
He needs constant injections just to stay alive.
I need to see it with my own eyes.
It's a secured lab.
You'll never be able to see it.
You'll never be able to get in there.
Not without you.
Or you can't, Captain.
I promise.
Sam.
Probably my last time.
I love you.
Lex.
Adam's gone.
Was it worth it?
Sacrificing the lives of Dr. Tang and all those technicians just to get back into the
pharmaceutical business?
I hope you weren't as emotional as this with the police.
I just spent the last five hours covering for you.
I appreciate the gesture, son, but I told you I had nothing to do with the lab at Metron.
And I suppose you didn't have anything to do with those murders either.
Lex, even if I were the demonic father you make me out to be, you know I would never
do anything so sloppy.
But I'm not worried, son.
How can you be so cavalier?
Because I know that I have someone extremely competent in charge.
Hmm?
You wanted the project.
It's yours.
I'm trusting you to handle things.
Nice try, Dad.
But I'm not suiting up in the eleventh hour.
You've got to stay.
Clean up your own mess.
I thought I was getting used to seeing some pretty weird things around here,
but Lana, this was a massacre.
What about Adam?
Looks like he escaped.
But you think he killed them.
He obviously escaped from his cell and strangled his doctor.
Looks like the other victims were trying to stop him.
Hey, guys.
So after I promised to switch my long-distance service,
I finally got my guy at the phone company to track down the block number you called from.
Whose was it?
It was from a cell phone belonging to Gwen Burton.
Is that when you're about?
No. I have no idea who that is.
Why would I make a mistake?
I could call from her phone.
I don't know.
But it looks like we can rack up another one for our
can-you-hear-me-24-hours-from-now theory.
I looked into Mrs. Burton's phone records,
and there were no outgoing calls made from last night.
It's like the call you received came out of thin air.
Or a really different time zone.
Look, at least this gives us an advantage.
We know what's supposed to happen.
All we have to do is keep Adam away from Lana.
And make sure you don't get that cell phone.
Adam could be anywhere.
Yeah, maybe it's safer if we get you out to the farm.
Clark, what if we can't stop this from happening?
Mrs. Burton?
I know this is a strange question, but I work at the teen crisis hotline,
and we got a call from this number last night. Is it yours?
Yes.
But I didn't make any calls last night.
I'm sorry, there must be some mistake.
Would you know an Adam Knight?
He used to be a patient here.
We don't get too many patients down in accounts receivable.
Look, Mrs. Burton, I don't know how to explain this,
but I think your phone's gonna be used in a crime.
Tonight.
What did you say your name was?
Clark Kent.
Well, Clark, we have an excellent psychiatric staff here at the hospital.
I'd be happy to take you down to the admitting desk and...
I know I sound crazy, but is there a chance you lost your phone?
Actually, I lent it to my husband today.
He had to run some errands in Metropolis.
Would you call him?
Please.
Hello.
Hi, honey.
There's some kid here asking about the cell phone.
What, they come in person now?
Just tell him we're happy with our plan.
Ask him where he is.
Where are you?
I'm stuck outside the city on Route 17.
I got a flat, but I should be home by...
Len?
He's not answering.
I'm off Exc blush, man.
Then tell him to pick it up care, he'll be okay.
Okay or that the Earth's spinning around in the clouds,
and I won't be up here, what's your problem, uncle?
I better get to the door, kid.
Where is he?
Can't I see him around here, sir?
Let me know, Muscle.
Okay.
You take care of the kid, man.
Sounds evening, sonny.
Goodbye, sir.
No.
I must have been out for a minute.
I need to call the police.
You don't have your cell phone, do you?
No.
Here you go, Lana.
I know this old house can get drafty.
I'm sure Mrs. Kent won't mind.
Thanks, Mr. Kent. I really appreciate it.
Yeah, okay. Yeah, I'll tell him.
What did Clark say?
He missed Adam by a few minutes,
and Adam has the cell phone.
It's all starting to come true.
The storm.
The phone.
Don't you worry, Lana.
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
You know, I'm not doing any good just standing here.
The police are looking for the stolen vehicle and for him,
so if any leads come through,
they're gonna come through the police scanner at the Torridge.
Here, Chloe, I want you to take my truck.
The last thing we need tonight
is you getting stuck crossing the creek
in that little car of yours.
Thank you.
Lana, it's gonna be okay.
We've got lots of time.
The game hasn't even started yet.
Keep me posted.
Still no leads on Adam.
What about the serum?
What about it?
Adam knows it's the only thing keeping him alive.
He's gotta go after more of it.
Only problem is there's no more serum for Adam to find.
You know your father didn't get rid of all of it.
He must have a stash somewhere.
Let's just shut it up and get to work.
Okay.
Support us next time, guys.
Yeah.
We just wanna make sure this film is made nicely
because...
Your father's always just enjoyed you.
See?
blowing.
What about you?
Mr. T Goneal's driving.
I thought you were the hero?
No.
The charge.
The card?
Okay.
Where's Lana?
I don't know. I'm not her keeper.
Don't lie to me.
I was just at the towel and they said both you and Lana left together.
Where is she?
Why do you care so much?
She's got something that belongs to me.
Well, it's obviously not here.
And if I were you, I wouldn't be either.
Everybody's looking for you.
Isn't that Clark's truck?
No, it's my cousin's.
Something tells me that's not...
Ah!
What did the operations say?
You're covering for her.
Where is she?
Is she hiding at her old boyfriend?
No!
No.
Don't worry.
You'll be able to talk to her soon enough.
I'm sure when Mrs. Kent gets home,
she'd be happy to whip you up one of her specialties
when...
I'm afraid it's just black coffee.
Thanks.
I have some honey.
No, no, I'm good.
All right.
Sounds like my truck.
.
Molly!
No!
Come on!
You wink at me?
No!
Mother!
I know you're in there!
If you don't come out, I'll kill your boyfriend's father!
Get on the lawn for Chloe!
Adam!
Whatever you want!
Just don't hurt them anymore!
Come on!
Leave them alone, please!
Please, no!
Hurry up!
Let's go!
Shut up and get the truck!
You're gonna stand there and tell me you weren't working with them?
No!
You were working with Dr. Tang?
You can't deny you're behind this?
I'm the one who called the ambulance.
Why would I do that if I was involved in those murders?
Well...
Let's see what we got in the goodie bag.
Nothing that will incriminate me.
Except some memos signed by you as acting director of the lab.
I've never seen these before.
Amazing how that always happens.
I'm being set up.
And they're doing a pretty damn good job of it.
Take a breather.
Think about if you want to stick to that story.
You have to let me go.
Look, kid, your friend's been running off at the mouth for over an hour, fessing up.
So don't try and play the hero.
You're bluffing.
He didn't admit to anything because he didn't do anything.
You really think that?
Something tells me that you don't know your friend as well as you think you do.
Hey, Paul, the Vipers just took Roberts off the court.
He blew out his knee.
And guess who they pulled off the bench with five minutes in the fourth quarter?
Gunners.
Yeah.
That guy throws more bricks than a mason.
I have to go.
I'm sorry, were we keeping you from something?
Have you called my parents yet?
Yeah, no one's answered.
Well, I think the newspapers would find it interesting
that a minor was being held for questioning without his guardian.
It wouldn't take any long vacations.
We may need to bring you in for more questioning.
Yeah.
Okay, David.
Vipers lead 52 to 46, but the momentum...
Oh!
...has hit zero bucks.
Denali dribbles on the court.
Passes through the low post.
Rear face right.
He shoots, but Armageddon takes it off the rim.
Come on, throw the Matthews.
Which one is it?
It's over here.
Mario?
Come on.
Faster.
I put everything I found in the apartment in these boxes over here.
Where are my books?
I don't know which one I put them in.
Well, look.
Come on.
Hurry up.
I don't have a lot of time, Lana.
The white one.
Where is it?
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's the medicine.
I had three vials in there.
What'd you do with them?
I didn't touch them.
You liar!
Oh!
No!
What happened?
I came home and found your father and Chloe outside.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Adam has Lana and he has your dad's gun.
Police are looking for him now.
Do you know which way they headed?
I don't know. Adam keeps saying that Lana has something of his.
The serum.
I don't know. He already went to the town and the house.
I don't know where they were headed next.
I'm going to the youth center.
The only thing we know for sure is that Lana is going to make that call to the crisis hotline.
Clark, what good is that going to do? You've already heard the call.
It was cutting in and out.
You could barely hear half of it.
If I can figure out why that call was placed at the pass, then maybe I can stop that from happening.
If you get a clear connection, you think Lana will be able to tell you where she is?
What's the score?
61-59.
Okay.
Vipers.
Vipers!
Oh, damn it.
Lana.
Clark!
Vipers!
Clark, it's happening!
Three seconds left in the game.
Gunners and troopers.
He's got a gun!
And it's on his own.
It is gone.
That makes the score 61-55.
Vipers.
Please help me!
Mom!
Clark!
Clark, why aren't you picking up?
He's trying to kill me!
Please help me!
Clark!
Help me!
Run, Clark!
You lied to me!
Run, where are you?
I don't want to!
Help me!
Lana?
Are you okay?
Where's Adam?
You took that bullet.
It's impossible.
I saw you.
Now I know why Lionel sent me to watch you.
I guess I found what I was looking for.
Just a little too late.
Adam!
He's not going to stop me.
Clark...
I couldn't escape him.
How long do you think you can?
How long do you think I can keep partners with Rachel?
I don't know!
I won't Icon declared.
I'll take all your《C seviables«!
wanted to do this, but I couldn't frankly do it!
And I don't know how to hide it.
I have to solve it.
Pawpaw?
...And what?
Let's go.
FBI.
Once you boys hit the showers,
this case has been bumped up to varsity.
That's just like you guys.
We do the heavy lifting
and just show up for the prize.
This better be important.
Your lawyer may have friends in high places,
but I'm not a believer in the trickle-down theory.
I want to make a deal.
Why should I do that?
From what I understand,
they're building a strong case against you.
As flattered as I am to be the object of so much attention,
you and I both know I'm only the consolation prize.
I'm listening.
Tell the cops to drop the charges and give me immunity.
And I'll give you the biggest arrest of your career.
What are we talking about?
I'll help you bring down my father.
In no messed up way.
But trust me that they're not никак geling enough to catch you
And I'm making it important that you help enter blows
No, I won't leave you alone.
That's how they do it.
Good day, sir.
That's why I'm counting on you to get it right the first time.
Well, I suppose I could have a lab outfitted
and a trial underway within a year.
Dr. Burgin, I want you up and running by the end of the week.
A project like this requires time.
Time is a luxury I don't have, Doctor.
I have been, uh,
diagnosed with a rather unique...
liver disease, and, uh, I'm out of options.
Any luck?
No, I... I got lost at the first wormhole.
You know, half the world's scientists are still debating over Einstein's theories of time travel.
I don't think we're gonna crack it in one night.
Clark, there's still something I don't understand.
How did you get from the hotline to the storage unit in a split second?
It took me more than a few seconds.
Maybe it had something to do with the weird time anomaly.
You know, there's something that I don't understand, either.
Why did you call the hotline instead of the police?
Because, um...
I knew you'd be there.
Looks like we cheated fate.
Barely.
I was so afraid that I wouldn't get to you in time.
I know.
I spent the last 24 hours terrified of what might happen.
But it all turned out okay.
It made me realize how many decisions I make because I'm scared of how things will end up.
We both do our share of that.
Maybe it's time to stop being so afraid.
I've always thought that my life is so map-based.
I've always thought that my life is so mapped out for me.
But...
You know, maybe we have more control over the future than we think.
I'm sorry.
Beautiful Well, it's gun time.
It's gun time!
I've been waiting for an Fridayike!
Oh no.
Oh Matsui, uh-oh, the next episode is Thursday, right?
PlayStation puck...
Oh Chantly and Kanane don't be.
Well then...
I guess...
It's four.
I don't know.